John Moura

Software Engineer

Summary

I started my career in 2020 as a freelance developer using React, Node, and React Native, and since then, I have built and participated in various types of projects as a Fullstack Developer specializing in Node, React, Vue, Next, React Native, and Typescript.

Hard Skills

Typescript, React, React Native, Nextjs, Vuejs, Node, Ruby on Rails, Swift, Mongodb, PostgreSQL, MySQL

Soft Skills

Collaboration, Problem-solving, Communication, Time management, Resultoriented

Languages

English, Portuguese

Certifications

- React Native Certified Rocketseat
- Fullstack Web Delopment Resilia

Work Experience

Senior Mobile Engineer

Breaker19

ago., 2024 - ago., 2024

Breaker19 is an efficient oilfield trucking & hotshot marketplace. I worked on the refactoring and maintenance of the driver and buyer apps using React Native, Expo, and Swift. I didn't limit myself to mobile development, but also contributed to the backend using Laravel and PostgreSQL.

- Created and maintained the web portal for buyers and drivers.
- Work on location features and language features.
- Refactor the Database and API to get more performance.

Frontend Developer

Port Louis dez., 2021 - fev., 2022

During my time at Port Louis, I was responsible for maintaining a legal system using Vue.js, Node, and MySQL.

- I wrote unit tests with Jest.
- Fixed bugs.
- Created new features.

Software Engineer

Fetchly Labs - Software House

ago., 2022 - jun., 2024

Responsible for creating web and mobile systems using React, React Native, Node, Ruby on Rails, Django, Docker, Angular, and Vue. During my time at Fetchly, I independently developed systems when necessary and assisted other teams by leading and supporting backend and frontend developers, like:

- · Ecommerces.
- Financials softwares.
- Hospital Applications.

Fullstack Web Developer

Noclaf Tech - Software House

fev., 2022 - jun., 2022

During my time at Noclaf, I worked as a full-stack developer using React, Angular, Firebase, Node, and GraphQL. I participated in the development of:

- Management systems.
- E-commerce platforms.
- Educational Applications.

Freelance Developer

John Dev

jun., 2020 - ago., 2024

I began my career developing websites and mobile applications as a freelancer in my city using Next.js, React, Node, React Native, and MySQL. I developed:

- E-commerces.
- Landing pages.
- Mobile apps.
- Blogs.

Projects

YoResume

set., 2024 - out., 2024

https://www.yoresume.work/
Resume Builder made with Nextjs, Prisma, Mongodb, TailwindCSS and Typescript

+1000 users are using YoResume!